Nighttime and Idols
Now then.
We've got the main event of the night, so let's get to it.
The main project of the night, the title call.
Can I ask you to be cute?
Yes, of course.
My three main elements.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
The three things that make you Tanaka-san.
Doo-doo! It's like this.
Okay, first of all, from number one to number three, can you say them?
First, he's a jack-of-all-trades.
The second is the number of words.
And the third and final one is "nerd kiss.
I see.
I put a crown on it like number one, but I didn't...
I made it look like a kiss kissing thing.
I don't know... it's just that he's the best at everything. What's this?
I don't know. It might sound a bit harsh to say that I can do pretty much anything, but I can do anything.
I can do anything.
Oh, I see.
I can't think of any other words to describe it.
That's great, isn't it?
I can only say that I can do anything.
That's right. You seem like an arrogant person.
No, no, not at all.
What can you do, for example?
For example, if I were an idol, I could do dancing.
Or, for example, if you are an idol, you can dance very well, and if you are an ordinary person, you can do handicrafts, cooking, games, and so on.
Crafts, cooking, games... I'm just saying.
I can do pretty much anything if I'm asked to do it.
Really?
Well, excuse me, Mr. Tanaka, but I'm thinking of going bouldering on location.
Can you climb?
Yes, I can.
Then, may I ask you to do the harmony of wisdom?
Yes, that would be great. I've been interested in it for a long time.
Well, if that's the answer, you can do anything, can't you?
But I don't often make mistakes.
So, if I make a mistake, I might not be able to get a picture of it.
That's a card I have to play.
But I can't go all the way up to the "Myles" level. It's too difficult.
It's too difficult. It's like, "Adults can do it.
It's like that.
But you don't want people to see that you did it, right?
Yes, I don't want to show it too much.
That's something that idols would want to see.
It would be nice if you could do that naturally.
I see.
There are some things you really can't do.
I can eat insects, for example.
But I don't want to be so excited about it. I think it's a judgment that since they can eat, they should eat as much as anyone else.
I was made to eat it once in a TV show when I said I wanted to try it.
It was more out of my own interest than idol-like.
It is your policy.
That's right.
That's the only reason I can do mimicry.
I don't know. I don't know.
I like it. I don't know.
I might not be good at it.
Oh, you're still going to ask. Even if you have to change it.
I don't want to do something I don't want to do.
I think I'll stop for a bit.
What kind of things?
Well, to some extent, on average, Mr. Tanaka says you can do it.
That's right.
He doesn't want to say that it's not easy to do.
Well, yes.
But even if you say you can't do it, there are more things you can do.
Oh, I see.
So, you are saying that even while transferring the information.
Actually.
If I say too much, you'll look at me like that next time.
No, no, I'm looking at you that way.
Please don't do that.
Maybe that's how Popper has been looking at me.
Maybe.
Well, you can manage to some extent.
They often say that. They think I'm a star pirate.
A star prostitute?
I think the environment in which I live is normal.
I see.
I don't know.
This program...
Mr. Tommy.
Mr. Kazuo Sagamino
Mr. Fumi Mix Fry
Mr. Kiarina Ise
This program was provided by Mr. Cranky Z.
Thank you very much.
Please see us again next time!
rock, paper, scissors
Hmmm...